You might have heard of some people considering suing their former employers for being bullied or for having to work overtime without being paid.
你可能听说过有些人考虑起诉他们的前雇主，原因是曾遭受欺凌或者被迫无薪加班。
But have you heard of a person taking their employer to court because the work was too boring?
但是，因为雇主给的工作太无聊而将其告上法庭，这种情况你听说过吗？
That's exactly what Frederic Desnard, a 44-year-old Frenchman did.
这正是44岁的法国人弗雷德里克·德萨纳德所做的事情。
He claimed that his bosses at a prestigious perfume company stripped him of meaningful tasks in his managerial job and gave him duties which were so dull they affected his health.
他声称，在一家著名的香水公司，他的老板们剥夺了他管理工作中有意义的任务，给他安排的职责非常枯燥，以至于影响了他的健康。
Desnard told French news agency AFP: "I went into depression, I was ashamed to be paid to do nothing".
德萨纳德告诉法新社：“我陷入了抑郁，拿着工资却什么都不做，我感到很羞愧。”
He went on sick leave for seven months and was fired in 2014.
他请了7个月的病假，然后在2014年被解雇了。
The former employee wanted €360,000 in compensation.
这位前雇员要求获得36万欧元的赔偿。
Some people might argue that being bored should almost be part of the job description.
有些人可能会争辩说，无聊几乎应该是工作描述的一部分。
Lars Fredrik Svendsen, author of 'A Philosophy of Boredom' and Professor of Philosophy at the University of Bergen, says, "Most of the words for work in various languages tend to tell that it's a really unpleasant phenomenon.
《无聊的哲学》一书的作者、卑尔根大学哲学教授拉尔斯·弗雷德里克·斯文森说：“各种语言中，大多数表示工作的词汇往往都表明工作是一种非常令人不愉快的现象。
The French word travail goes back to the trepallum, it was a word for a torture instrument."
法语单词travail可以追溯到trepallum，这个词原本是一种刑具的名称。”
So should employers really care if their staff are bored to death as long as they do their tasks?
那么，只要员工完成了任务，雇主真的应该在意他们是否无聊得要命吗？
Svendsen thinks it is in their interest to have a stimulated workforce.
斯文森认为，拥有一支积极进取的员工队伍符合雇主的利益。
The academic says, "Employees who care about what they do tend to do a better job than those who don't.
这位学者说：“关心自己工作的员工往往比那些不关心的员工工作做得更好。
It will probably be wise for employers to at least facilitate some perception of meaning at work.
对雇主来说，至少促进员工对工作意义的某种认知可能是明智之举。
Let the workers feel that their work is meaningful to them."
让员工觉得他们的工作对自己是有意义的。”
In any case, Desnard might have been better off finding some meaning in his dull work as his action brought him some notoriety and not much else.
无论如何，德萨纳德或许当初在他枯燥的工作中找到一些意义会更好，因为他的行为只给他带来了一些恶名，别的收获寥寥。
A court in France didn't see things the same way he did and ordered Desnard to pay his former employer €1,000 for defamation.
法国的一家法院并不认同他的观点，并且责令德萨纳德因诽谤向前雇主支付1000欧元。